Guide to the Lucy Monroe Calhoun Family Photographs and Papers, 1886-1993 and undated, bulk 1911-1933 RL.11103
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Developing out paper and gelatin silver photographs, 1900-1941 and undated; 1
  - Lucy's residences, 1910-1929; 1
    - Corner of salon, with fur on k'ang, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-054.2)
      Copy of RL11103-P-054.1.
    - Corner of salon, with fur on k'ang, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-054.3)
      Copy of RL11103-P-054.1. Photograph has black border.
    - Corner of salon, with fur on k'ang, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-054.4)
      Version of RL11103-P-054.1.
    - Corner of salon, with bolsters on k'ang and fur rug, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-055.1)
      沙龙一角，炕椅上放着靠枕和皮毛地毯
    - Corner of salon, with bolsters on k'ang and fur rug, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-055.2)
      Copy of RL11103-P-055.1.
    - Sung jar in hall leading to dining room., 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-056.1)
      条案上的宋代瓷瓶，通向餐厅
      Gallery
    - Sung jar in hall leading to dining room., 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-056.2)
      Peking. Hall leading to dining room. Gray coolie cloth hangings, gray wood furniture. Sung jar.
      Version of RL11103-P-056.1.
    - Buddaist Sculpture, North end of gallery?, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-057.1)
      条案上的佛塑像，陈列室北面（？）
    - Buddaist Sculpture, North end of gallery?, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-057.2)
      Copy of RL11103-P-057.1.
    - Buddaist Sculpture, North end of gallery?, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-057.3)
    - Buddaist Sculpture, North end of gallery?, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-057.4)
      Version of RL11103-P-057.1.
    - Buddaist Sculpture, North end of gallery?, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-057.5)
    - Lucy's? bedroom, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-058.1)
      露西（？）卧室
    - Lucy's? bedroom, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-058.2)
      my bedroom
      Version of RL11103-P-058.1.
    - Decorative screen., 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-059.1)
      用来装饰的屏风
    - Decorative screen., 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-059.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-059.1.
    - The gallery, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-060.1)
      陈列室
    - The gallery, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-060.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-060.1.
    - Buddaist Sculpture, North end of gallery?, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-061.1)
    - Buddaist Sculpture, North end of gallery?, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-061.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-061.1.
    - Buddaist Sculpture, North end of gallery?, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-061.3)
    - Buddaist Sculpture, North end of gallery?, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-061.4)
    - South end of gallery, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-062.1)
    - South end of gallery, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-062.2)
      Copy of RL11103-P-062.1.
    - South end of gallery, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-062.3)
      Version of RL11103-P-062.1. Photograph has black border.
    - South end of gallery, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-062.4)
      Version of RL11103-P-062.1.
    - South end of gallery, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-062.5)
      Gallery, south end.
    - Corner of gallery, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-063)
      陈列室一角
    - Two women with blooming plants, corner of gallery, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-064)
      两位女士站在陈列室一角的盆栽花旁
    - Bedroom., 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-065.1)
      卧室
    - Bedroom., 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-065.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-065.1.
    - Polly Root Collier seated in living room near flowering plant, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-066)
      波莉·鲁特·科利尔坐在会客室，旁边是开花的大盆栽
      PRC. Polly Root Collier
    - Polly Root Collier standing at entrance to Lucy's house, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-067)
      波莉·鲁特·科利尔站在露西的房前
    - A Manchu princess seated in the gallery, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-068)
      一位满族格格坐在陈列室
      Manchu princess
    - Mrs. Wu Lien-Teh (Huang Shuqiong) in gallery entrance, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-069.1)
      伍连德夫人黄淑琼站在陈列室门口
      Mrs. Wu Lien-Teh
    - Mrs. Wu Lien-Teh (Huang Shuqiong) in gallery entrance, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-069.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-069.1.
    - Mrs. Wu Lien-Teh (Huang Shuqiong) near chest in gallery, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-070)
      伍连德夫人黄淑琼站在陈列室的柜子旁
    - Mrs. Wu Lien-Teh (Huang Shuqiong) in courtyard, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-071)
      伍连德夫人黄淑琼站在院中
    - Manchu royalty stand on Lucy's porch: unknown, Mme Hao, Duchess Tsai Tze, unknown Mme Sai, Chia Ko Ko, E. Ko Ko, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-072)
      皇族福晋和格格们在露西的院子里：郝夫人，载泽福晋和她的两个女儿，傅伦福晋和她的两个女儿
      2 Mme Hao 4 Little Princess 3 Duchess Tsai Tze 5 Mme Sai 6 Cha Ko Ko 7 E. Ko Ko
    - Ma in gallery, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-073)
      马管家站在陈列室
      Ma in gallery
    - Unidentified group of women seated in living room, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-074)
      起居室坐在里的几位女士
    - Lucy Calhoun, one of her dog's, and an unidentified visitor stand at the entrance to her house. Ma stands in the doorway., 1920s; 4.5 x 3.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-075.1)
      露西·嘉乐恒抱着小狗和一位来客站在门口，后面站在马管家
    - Lucy Calhoun, one of her dog's, and an unidentified visitor stand at the entrance to her house. Ma stands in the doorway., 1920s; 4.5 x 3.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-075.2)
      Copy of RL11103-P-075.1.
    - Kung monk? with scrolls in the gallery, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-076)
      和尚？坐在陈列室，地板上都是卷轴
      Kung
    - Ma (at right) and another man sitting in servant's? courtyard, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-077)
      马管家站在右边，另一人坐在院中，仆人住的院子？
    - Ma (middle) and two other servants standing in servant's? courtyard, 1920s; 4 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-078)
      马管家在中间，和两位仆人在仆人住的院子里？
    - Sedan chairs in front of Legation house, 1910s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-079)
      公使馆 前的轿子
    - Sedan chairs leaving the Legation house; troops offer salute, 1912; 6.5 x 4.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-080)
      坐轿离开公使馆，士兵们敬礼
      April 21. The Salute. Uncle leaving Legation, "Call out the guard."
    - Sedan chairs in green and yellow sent from the Court, 1912; 6.5 x 4.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-081)
      黄绿色大轿从清宫回来
      April 21, 1912. Peking. Sedan chairs in green and yellow sent from the Court.
    - William J.Calhoun on his way to the Audience with the Regent, 1912; 6.5 x 4.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-082)
      威廉·J.·嘉乐恒坐轿去面见清摄政王
      April 21. W.J.C. on his way to the Audience with the Regent.
  - Beijing, 1910-1941; 2
    - Prince Tsai Tao's son and daughter at the Moon Gate, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 23, Image RL11103-N-002)
      贝勒载涛的儿子溥佳和女儿韞慧站在月亮门
      Negative of RL11103-P-167. Note on folder: Prince Tsai Tao's son & daughter. [he was] last emperor Puyi's uncle. [she] became Mongolia's king's wife
    - Alex Kirk's Peking garden, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 23, Image RL11103-N-007)
      亚历克丝·柯克在北京的花园
      Negative of RL11103-P-546.
    - Five Pagoda Temple, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-083)
      五塔寺
      Five Pagoda Temple
    - Yellow Temple, corner of roof and side of building, 1920s; 3.25 x 5.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-084)
      西黄寺？大殿一边和屋檐一角
      Yellow Temple?
    - approach to the Yellow Temple, 1920s; 3.25 x 5.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-085)
      西黄寺正门
      Yellow Temple
    - At the Yellow Temple, 1920s; 3.25 x 5.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-086)
      西黄寺中
      At the Yellow Temple
    - Yellow Temple in detail, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-087)
      西黄寺中石刻
      Detail--Yellow Temple
    - Little boy at Yellow Temple, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-088)
      西黄寺中的小孩
      Little girl at Yellow Temple [Illegible?]
      Original caption incorrectly identifies this as a little girl.
    - Kids at the Lama Temple, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-089)
      五个孩子，雍和宫
      At the Lama Temple
    - Lama Temple lion, 1920s; 3.25 x 5.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-090)
      雍和宫的石狮子
      Lama Temple lion
    - Lama Temple, with monks, 1920s; 3.25 x 5.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-091)
      雍和宫的喇嘛们
      Llama Temple
    - Lung Fu Ssu (Longfu Temple), 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-092)
      隆福寺
      Lung Fu ssu
    - Ten Thousand Buddhas Temple, 1920s; 4 x 2.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-093)
      万佛寺
      Ten Thousand Buddhas Temple
    - Right to left: General McCoy, W. H. Donald, Marshal Chang Hsueh Liang, 1932 September 4; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 5, Print RL11103-P-094)
      从右到左：麦考益將军，威廉.亨利.端纳 以及张学良将军
      Right to left: General McCoy, W. H. Donald, Marshal Chang Hsueh Liang
    - Departure of League of Nations Commission, Aldrovandi Italian; General McCoy, American; Lord Lytton, British; Marshal Chang Hsueh Liang, 1932 September 4; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 5, Print RL11103-P-095)
      国联调查团离开（离开北京去上海）：意大利人马柯迪, 美国人麦考益将军, 英国人李顿爵士（团长）以及张学良将军
      Sept. 4. Departure of League of Nations Commission. [illegible] Aldebrandi, Italian General McCoy, American Lord Lytton, British Marshal Chang Hsueh Liang
    - Marshal Chang Hsueh Liang, 1932 September 4; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 5, Print RL11103-P-096)
      张学良将军
      Marshal Chang Hsueh Liang
    - Ching Huo airport. General & Mrs. McCoy, Count Aldrovandi, 1932 September 4; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 5, Print RL11103-P-097)
      麥考益将军和夫人，马柯迪伯爵
      Sept. 4 1932. Ching Huo airport. General & Mrs. McCoy, Count Aldebrandi
    - Mrs. General McCoy, Dr. Schnee, (German member), Mrs. Walter Young, 1932 September 4; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 5, Print RL11103-P-098)
      麥考益将军夫人，希尼博士（德国代表）, (美国)杨华德夫人
      Mrs. General McCoy, Dr. Schnee, (German member), Mrs. Walter Young
    - Ching Huo airport. Marshal Chang Hsueh Liang's Ford tri-motor plane, 1932 September 4; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 5, Print RL11103-P-099)
      张学良将军的福特三摩托飞机，北京机场
      Ching Huo airport. Marshal Chang Hsueh Liang's Ford tri-motor plane.
    - Coal Hill Temple, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-100)
      煤山（景山）绮望楼
      Coal Hill Temple
    - Coal Hill Temple gates, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-101)
      煤山（景山）西牌坊（额曰"舊典時式"）
    - From Central Park, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-102)
      中央公园（中山公园）：松柏交翠亭 （六方亭）
      From Central Park
    - Central Park trees, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-103)
      中央公园（中山公园）：古树
      Central Park
    - Central park willow tree branches and lotus? flowers, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-104)
      中央公园（中山公园）：荷叶
    - The Forbidden City, showing Wu Men （Meridian Gate); the Great Court with 5 marble bridges(Golden Water Bridge), and Tai Ho Tien (Hall of Supreme Harmony), 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-105)
      紫禁城俯瞰（午门、金水桥、太和门及太和殿）
      The Forbidden City, showing Wu Men; the Great Court with 5 marble bridges, and Tai Ho Tien. Also the T'ai U[nao] (extreme right).
    - An entrance to the Forbidden City, 1920s; 5.25 x 3 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-106)
      紫禁城宫门（乾清门？）
      [(Crossed out:) Ming tombs?] An entrance to the Forbidden City
    - Golden Water, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-107)
      金水河（及金水桥）
      Forbidden City
    - Chinese lion in the Forbidden City, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-108.1)
      紫禁城里的鎏金铜狮（太和门前）
    - Chinese lion in the Forbidden City, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-108.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-108.1. Photograph has black border.
    - Gate of Supreme Harmony, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-109)
      太和门
    - Marble steps in the Forbidden City, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-110)
      紫禁城（太和）殿前石阶
    - bronze crane and a bronze tortoise in front of the Hall of Supreme Harmony in the Forbidden City, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-111)
      紫禁城太和殿前宽阔的丹陛上陈设的铜鹤及铜龟
    - Marble carriageway in front of the Hall of Supreme Harmony, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-112)
      紫禁城太和殿前御道的汉白玉石雕
    - Lions and cauldrons in front of the The Gate of Heavenly Purity, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-113)
      乾清门前大铜缸及鎏金铜狮
    - Qilin guardians at Gate of Benevolent Peace, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-114)
      慈宁门前麒麟
    - Building and marble steps in the Forbidden City, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-115)
      紫禁城大殿（保和殿？）的汉白玉台基
    - Water spouts along walkway in the Forbidden City, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-116)
      大殿台基上的龙头形状的离首
    - Throne in the Palace of Heavenly Purity, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-117)
      乾清宫御座
      [Throne?] in the Forbidden City
    - Forbidden City--Central Park. Canal near bridge--with one corner tower, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-118.1)
      紫禁城角楼及护城河
      Forbidden City--Central Park. Canal near bridge--with one corner tower
    - Forbidden City--Central Park. Canal near bridge--with one corner tower, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-118.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-118.1. Photograph has black border.
    - Forbidden City--Central Park. Canal near bridge--with one corner tower, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-118.3)
      Version of RL11103-P-118.1.
    - Emperor Hsuan T'ung (Xuantong), 1910s; 3 x 5.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-119)
      宣统皇帝溥仪
      His Majesty Hsuan T'ung [This]
    - Chung Hai (Zhong Hai), 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-120)
      中海
      Chung Hai
    - Silver pines in front of Wanshan Hall, Zhong Hai, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-473)
      中海万善殿前的松树
    - Nan Hai stairway, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-121)
      南海瀛台石阶
      Winter Palace. Nan Hai
    - Nan Hai canal, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-122)
      南海水渠
      Nan Hai
    - Nan Hai railing detail, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-123)
      南海淑清院万字廊
    - Soldier at Nan Hai, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-124)
      南海护卫
    - Nan Hai temple, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-125)
      南海万善殿
      Nan Hai temple
    - Chinese lion at Nan Hai, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-126)
      南海铜狮
    - Trees and plantings at Nan Hai, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-127)
      南海古树
    - Canal and pavilion at Nan Hai, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-128)
    - Pavilion of the Water and Cloud, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-129.1)
      中海水云榭
      Zhong Hai
    - Pavilion of the Water and Cloud, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-129.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-129.1. Photograph has black border.
    - Railing detail and structures at Nan Hai, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-130)
      南海双环亭（凤亭）
    - Building and canal at Nan Hai, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-131)
      南海淑清院水渠
    - Nan Hai temple with tree, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-132)
      南海万善殿前古树
    - Nan Hai tea garden, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-133)
      南海静园
      Nan Hai tea garden
    - Winter Palace at Pei Hai (Bei Hai), 1920s; 4 x 2.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-134)
      北海白塔
      Winter Palace
    - Winter Palace at Pei Hai (Bei Hai), 1920s; 2.5 x 4 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-135)
    - Pei Hai (Bei Hai). Chuang Kuan Fu (close), 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-136)
      北海（澄观堂）
      Pei Hai. Chuang Kuan Fu
    - Pei Hai (Bei Hai). Chuang Kuan Fu (close), 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-137)
    - Nine Dragon Wall at Pei Hai (Bei Hai), 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-138)
      北海九龙壁
      Forbidden City. The Pei Hai
    - Porcelain temple at Pei Hai (Bei Hai), 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-139)
      北海西天梵境的琉璃阁
      Porcelain temple-- green & yellow--in Pei Hai
    - Monument to Dalai Lama of Tibet, Chung Lung, Pei Hai (Bei Hai), 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-140)
      北海白塔（为迎接五世达赖喇嘛来京朝觐）
      Forbidden City--Pei Hai. Monument to Dalai Lama of Thibet. Chung Lung
    - Pei Hai (Bei Hai) rock garden, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-141)
      北海静心斋太湖石景
      Pei Hai rock garden
    - Pei Hai (Bei Hai) rock garden, with stairs, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-142)
    - Pei Hai (Bei Hai) rock garden, with bridge, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-143)
      北海静心斋太湖石景及石桥
    - Porcelain Temple from below, Pei Hai (Bei Hai), 1920s; 5.25 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-144)
      北海万佛楼
    - Porcelain Temple from rock garden, Pei Hai (Bei Hai), 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-145.1)
      从静心斋看北海万佛楼
      Pei Hai from the Rock Garden--yellow and green porcelain temple
    - Porcelain Temple from rock garden, Pei Hai (Bei Hai), 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-145.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-145.1. Photograph has black border.
    - Wall and Porcelain temple, Pei Hai (Bei Hai), 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-146)
      Pei Hai
    - Pei Hai (Bei Hai) near rock garden, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-147)
      北海静心斋附近
      Pei Hai near rock garden
    - Pei Hai (Bei Hai) white jade Kwan yin, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-148)
      北海白玉观音像
      Pei Hai white jade Kwan yin
    - Pei Hai (Bei Hai) walkways, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-149)
      北海 桥
    - Green jade bowl at Pei Hai (Bei Hai), 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-150)
      北海的渎山大玉海
      Pei Hai--Green Jade Bowl
    - Pei Hai (Bei Hai) gate, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-151)
      北海大门
    - Pei Hai (Bei Hai) courtyard, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-152)
      北海的一处庭院
    - Five Dragons Pavilion, Pei Hai (Bei Hai), 1920s; 4 x 2.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-153)
      北海五龙亭
      Five Dragons Pavilion
    - "The Purple Cows," Peking, 1912. In front: Casenave, Pierre de Margerie, Beatrice de Menocal, John Russell, Uncle Cal. Back: Aunt Lucy, [Dorothy] Straight, Mabel Russell, Dan de Menocal, Polly, Willard Straight, 5.5 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 10, Print RL11103-P-154)
      1912年北京，前排是贾思纳、马士理、比阿特丽斯·德曼诺克、约翰·拉塞尔、嘉乐恒；后排是：露西、多萝西·司戴德、梅布尔·拉塞尔、丹·德曼诺克、波莉、威廉·司戴德
      "The Purple Cows" Peking 1912. In front: Casenave, de Margery, Beatrice de Menocal, John Russell, Uncle Cal. Back: Aunt Lucy, Beatrice Straight, Mabel Russell, Dan de Menocal, Polly, Willard Straight
    - "The Purple Cows." Front row: P. de Margerie, Casenaves, Major Russell, Uncle Cal, Aunt Lucy. Back row: D. de Menocal, Mabel Russell, Beatrice de Menocal, Polly, Dorothy & Willard Straight, 1910s; 6 x 4 in. (Box 1, Folder 10, Print RL11103-P-155)
      前排：马士理、贾思纳、拉塞尔少校、嘉乐恒、露西；后排：丹·德曼诺克、梅布尔·拉塞尔、比阿特丽斯·德曼诺克、波利、桃乐西·司戴德、威廉·司戴德
      "The Purple Cows." Front row: P. de Margerie, Casenaves, Major Russell, Uncle Cal, Aunt Lucy. Back row: D. de Menocal, Mabel Russell, Beatrice de Menocal, Polly, Dorothy & Willard Straight
    - Russian party at Bill Drummond's, 1920s; 4.25 x 3 in. (Box 1, Folder 10, Print RL11103-P-156)
      比尔·德拉蒙德家的俄罗斯派对
      Russian party at Bill Drummond's
    - Lucy Calhoun, seated, during Russian party, 1920s; 4.25 x 3 in. (Box 1, Folder 10, Print RL11103-P-157)
      露西·嘉乐恒居中坐着，俄罗斯派对
    - Woman standing in front of Lucy Calhoun, seated, at Russian party, 1920s; 4.25 x 3 in. (Box 1, Folder 10, Print RL11103-P-158)
      露西·嘉乐恒居中坐着，一位女士站在她对面，俄罗斯派对
    - Full cast of play "It Pays to Advertise," Peking, 1927, 9.5 x 7.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 10, Print RL11103-P-159)
      1927年北京演出"广告的效果"剧目的所有演员
      It Pays to Advertise, Peking, 1927
    - Cast of play "It Pays to Advertise" with soap advertsing sign, 1927; 9.5 x 7.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 10, Print RL11103-P-160)
      演出"广告的效果"剧目的所有演员及肥皂广告图
      It Pays to Advertise, Peking
    - Cast of Captain Applejack, 1927. Max Merkerk to left. Mayo Newhall at my left. Peking, 9.5 x 7.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 10, Print RL11103-P-161)
      1927年在北京演出Captain Applejack，左边是马克斯·默克，我的左边是梅奥·纽霍尔
      Captain Applejack, 1927. Max Merkerk to left. Mayo Newhall at my left. Peking.
    - Marco Polo bridge, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-162)
      卢沟桥
      The Western Hills--Peking. Marco Polo Bridge
    - Signed: Very sincerely yours, Leefong [ethlo] Peking 17 Feb 13, 1913 February 2; 4.75 x 7.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-163)
      签名：您最真诚的Leefong北京1917年2月13日
      Very sincerely yours, Leefong [ethlo] Peking 17 Feb 13
    - Military officers and legation? officials, Yuan Shih K'ai and William J. Calhoun, center, 1910s; 10 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-164)
      袁世凯和威廉·嘉乐恒和其他人的合影
    - William J. Calhoun and Yuan Shih K'ai, 1912 February 20; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-165)
      袁世凯和威廉·嘉乐恒
      W. J. C. & Yuan Shih K'ai, Peking, February 20, 1912
    - Casenave & Willard Straight, 1920s; 3 x 5.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-166)
      贾思纳和威廉·司戴德
      Peking. Casenave & Willard Straight
    - Prince Tsai Tao's son and daughter at the Moon Gate, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-167)
      The Moon Gate. Prince Tsai Tao's son and daughter
    - Opra singer Mei Lanfang, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-168)
      梅兰芳
    - Mrs. Alfred Sze, 1911 May; 3.75 x 5.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-169)
      施肇基夫人施唐钰华
      K. T. Thompson, Mrs. Alfred Sze, May 1911
    - Mrs. Alfred Sze's children, 1910s; 3.75 x 5.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-170)
      施肇基儿子施耿元和女儿施蕴珍
      K. T. Thompson, Mrs. Alfred Sze's children
    - Ann Carrère seated in the courtyard at 10 Tsui [Hua] Hutung, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-171)
      安·卡雷尔坐在翠花胡同10号的院子里
      June 1922. Peking. Courtyard at 10 Tsui [Huan] Hutung
    - Prince Tsai Tao at his summer place, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-172)
      贝勒载涛在他避暑的宅子里
      Prince Tsai Tao at his summer place